ntop.org 2019-08-12

# Privacy Policy – ntop

* * *

### GDPR Compliancy

ntop grants you the respect of privacy protection laws and [GDPR 679/2016](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/General_Data_Protection_Regulation), in particular as specified in Articles 13 to 22, and 34. At any time you can [contact the data protection officer](https://www.ntop/support/need-help-2/contact-us/) Luca Deri to request information about this matter. We grant you that collected information (for instance your name and email when you contact us) will be used only for complying with regulatory laws and will not be disclosed to third party as specified later in this page. At any time you can contact us to access your personal data, modify or ask us to delete them as of Art 18.

### Website Visitors

ntop collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. ntop’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how ntop’s visitors use its website.

### Aggregated Statistics

ntop may collect aggregated statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, ntop may reveal how many downloads a particular software version got. However, ntop does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

ntop discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees or contractors that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on ntop’s behalf or to provide services available at ntop’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees and contractors may be located outside of your home country. ntop will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees and contractors, as described above, ntop discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when ntop believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of ntop, third parties, or the public at large. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. ntop takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. ntop uses cookies to help ntop identify and track visitors, their usage of ntop website, and their website access preferences. ntop visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using ntop’s websites.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, ntop may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in ntop’s sole discretion. ntop encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
